# Nguyễn Oanh

# **Tester**

Mobile: 01683246901 - Email: oanhmeo.tina51@gmail.com

# **ABOUT ME**



I am Nguyễn Thị Oanh, I have more than 2 years experience in web, mobile, desktop testing. I am currently working at Fruity Solution LTD at position of tester leader. My objective now is to complete the assigned task successfully. My plan in next 5 years is to become a Business Analysist with the higher income.

#### **SKILLS**

English	•	•	•	•	0
Test	•	•	•	•	•
Writing	•	•	•	•	

## **EDUCATION**

1999 - 2003 I was best at Math.

Hà Vinh Secondary School at Thanh Hóa

2003-2006 I participated in Math contest with 2nd prize.

Tran Phu High School at Thanh Hóa

2006 - 2011 I studied Information Technology with good grade

University of Agriculture

# **EXPERIENCE**

2011-2011 GVC Organization

Document writer

I designed access template and input data for it

2011-2012 IVG JSC.

Tester

Assure quality of CRM web application. Understand requirement, design test plan, test case. Execute test

and Test report. Write user guide.

2012-2014 Fruity Solution LTD.

Test leader

Manage testing team assuring all the products of company is in good quality. My task is designing test

plan, test case, writing document and project

management.